# Viprajay Dhali

Software Developer

Enthusiastic Software Developer with a flair for creating elegant solutions in the least amount of the time Having experience of more than one year wherein I've built solutions for many technical firms. I aim and work to establish Myself as a BRAND in this technical industry.





dhaliviprajay@gmail.com



Rudrapur, India



github.com/viprajay

+91 798396053

in LinkedIn

</> GeeksForGeeks / LeetCode

### **MY PROJECT**

#### 1 .NBCT SKILL DEVELOPMENT

Achievements/Tasks

National Board of Computer Technology (NBCT) aims to impart basic information about necessity of computer literacy in various fields, with quality knowledge.

### 2.NANAK TRADERS

Achievements/Tasks

Nanak cards is an Indian Wedding cards, visiting cards and wood frame Website where you can find the best wedding cards.

### 3 .NBCT DIGITAL INDIA

Achievements/Tasks

National Board of Computer Technology (NBCT) aims to impart basic information about necessity of computer literacy in various fields, with quality knowledge.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Software Developer**

DigiAffecs

(Present)

Managing the websites and also creating new websites.

### Jr. Software Developer

Parvati and Sons

(08/2020 - 07/2021)

Developed many websites that are using by many users.

### **Web Development Intern**

Parvati and Sons

(02/2020 - 07/2020)

Developed the Admin Panel where we can see the details of products in E-commerce website.

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- 1. Participated in CANVAS"Shades of Talent":-Volleyball,kho-kho
- 2. Got 1<sup>st</sup> place in quiz competition
- 3. Got 2<sup>nd</sup> place in"MAHA-PURSHO KO JANO" quiz competition
- 4. Got 2<sup>nd</sup> place in running competition
- 5 . Participate in "Cultural activities"

### <u>SKILLS</u>



### **EDUCATION**

#### **MCA**

(08/2023 - Pursuing)
Quantum University, Roorkee

#### **PGDCA**

(08/2021 - 07/2022) Droan Group of colleges, Rudrapur

#### **BCA**

(08/2017 - 07/2020) Droan Group of colleges, Rudrapur

### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

### 1. WhataApp Chat Analyzer

\* Analyzing WhatsApp chat is a time-consuming task So I want to save time. WhatsApp Chat Analyzer has the potential to provide valuable analysis and facilitate effective communication.

#### 2. Text Emotion Detection

\* Emotion Detection is the sentiment analysis process used to extract emotions from the text that best represent the author's mental state.

#### 3. IPL Win & Loss Predictor

\* IPL Win and Loss Predictor" project! This machine learning model, built using logistic regression, predicts the probability of a team winning an IPL match based on the current match situation.

## **ORGANIZATIONS**

- 1. Codefest-1
- 2. Codefest-2
- 3. Innovation Fair
- 4. Intra University Rapid Chess Championship
- 5 . Computer Hardware Maintenance Workshop